{
    "subject": "Kenneth_Branagh",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "The_Magic_Flute__2006_film_",
    "human_readable": "Kenneth Branagh directed The Magic Flute (2006 film).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9259936809539795,
            "question": "Who directed the 2006 film adaptation of The Magic Flute?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8273884057998657,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Kenneth Branagh."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7620586156845093,
            "question": "Kenneth Branagh is known for directing which genre of films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6695201396942139,
            "question": "What type of production was The Magic Flute (2006)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6350266337394714,
            "question": "What is the name of the film director who worked on The Magic Flute?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6011654734611511,
            "question": "Is there a movie adaptation of The Magic Flute?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5441176891326904,
            "question": "Who is responsible for bringing The Magic Flute to the big screen in 2006?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5425330400466919,
            "question": "What year was the film version of The Magic Flute released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45205771923065186,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Kenneth Branagh that features Mozart's opera?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44502678513526917,
            "question": "Which famous opera did Kenneth Branagh direct a movie adaptation of?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kenneth Branagh directed The Magic Flute (2006 film).",
            "html": "yago_21992_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the title of the film directed by Kenneth Branagh that features Mozart's opera?",
            "html": "yago_21992_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the film version of The Magic Flute released?",
            "html": "yago_21992_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is responsible for bringing The Magic Flute to the big screen in 2006?",
            "html": "yago_21992_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21992_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21992_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21992_136.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21992_176.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21992_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21992_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21992_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21992_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21992_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21992_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support this triple. Specifically, document file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_21992/re-ranker-msmarco/82.txt states that \"The Magic Flute is Kenneth Branagh's English-language film version of Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart's singspiel Die Zauberfl\u00f6te.\", and document file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_21992/re-ranker-msmarco/104.txt mentions that Branagh was approached to make a film version of The Magic Flute in 2006."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Kenneth Branagh directed The Magic Flute (2006 film).\" Multiple sources confirm Branagh's direction of this opera film, including his comments in 2006 about being asked to direct Mozart\u2019s The Magic Flute and details regarding its production."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}